A Guide to the Robert Bolling Lambeth papers, 1921-2007
Library of Virginia
- Series XI: General publications., Extent: 1 box. (Box 25)
  - Fortune, April 1964. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Three Keys to Strength: Production, Stability, Free-World Unity. Third Quarterly Report to the President by the Director of Defense Mobilization, 1 October 1951. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Let's Join the Human Race by Stringfellow Barr, 1950 (10th impression 1953). (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Metropolitan Virginia 1967: A Brief Assessment. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - ,Norfolk: The Magazine of Norfolk, Virginia, February 1950, January 1951. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Notes on Surface Water in Virginia--Department of Conservatin and Economic Development, Division of Water Resources, December 1960. (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Our Foreign Policy, 1952. (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - The Ports of Greater Hampton Roads Annual, 1954. (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Public Affairs in Virginia, September 1954, July-September 1955, January[?] 1956. (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Museum programs, 1970-1971. (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Scenic Historyland. (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Virginia's Scenic Rivers: a Report by the Commission of Outdoor Recreation, 1969. (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - W and L: The Alumni Magazine of Washington and Lee University, April 1976. (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - We Remember Charlie: Recollections of the Late Judge Charles E. Burks of Lynchburg, Virginia, ca. 1980. (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Welcome Visitor: Official Guide to Tucson. (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - What Others Say: W. B. Barbour, D.C. Ph.C., 1948. (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Why Knowledge of the Laws of Human Behavior Makes for Success by Mark Embury Penney, Ph.D., 1921. (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Series XII: Advertisements., Extent: 1 box. (Box 26)
  Advertisements contains advertisements, catalogs, directories, maps, and other papers consisting of ads for clothes, Howard Johnson's motor lodges, mimeograph equipment, nautical equipment, office furniture, science equipment, silverware and service, tractors, and other items.
  - Howard Johnson's motor lodges, restaurants--directories, 1968-1970. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Howard Johnson's motor lodges, restaurants--directories, 1970-1972. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Howard Johnson's motor lodges, restaurants--directories, map, 1976-1977, undated. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Edmund Catalog: Science, Math, Optics, 1967. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - The Big Little Book of the Crow's Nest--Abercombie and Fitch, 1968. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Sterling Says It All: Your Sterling Silver Pattern Selector, 1978. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Mimeograph and duplication catalogs. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Office ads. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Tractor ads. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - General advertisements (folder 1 of 2). (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - General advertisements (folder 2 of 2). (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Series XIII: General subjects., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 26-28)
  - Agriculture and Farmers Union papers, 1953-1954, undated. (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Agriculture and Farmers Union clippings, 1953-1954, undated. (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Bedford County finances, 1948-1953. (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Bedford County history--clipings and booklet, 1907, 1950, undated. (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Biographies, political figures. (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - The Atlanta Century for 1862-1863 (Civil War) from the Atlanta Journal-Constitution, 1962-1963. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Civil War clippings, 1961-1963. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Confederate Museum newspapers. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Program for the 16th annual meeting of the League of Virginia Counties, 23-25 October 1950. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - County Action for Outdoor Recreation by National Association of Counties, 1964. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - County government clippings, 1953. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Fallout shelter and protection. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Report of the Virginia Mental Health Study Commission to the State Mental Health Authority, 31 March 1965. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Hospitals--clippings, 1949, 1952-1954, 1956. (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Hospitals--clippings, undated. (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Highways--papers, 1953, 1955, undated. (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Home and Highway, Summer 1963. (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Highway Users, April 1950. (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - The Virginia Roadbuilder, March-April 1950. (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Transportation and freight--clippings, ca. 1940-1941. (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Highways--clippings, 1952-1956. (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Highways--clippings, undated (ca. 1953-1954). (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Hunting papers, 1950-1976. (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Labor--papers, 1953-1954. (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Labor--clippings, ca. 1953-1955. (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Landscaping catalogs, etc. (Box 27, Folder 21)